吸血鬼后裔  前情提示
Previously on Legacies...
霍普  你不能把我留在这
Hope, you can't leave me here.
我没办法带你离开
I can't leave with you.
你是谁
Who are you?
全世界
The entire world
都已经忘记了我
has forgotten that I exist,
我爱的男孩也已经不再爱我
and the boy I love has moved on.
送我回去
Send me back,
我要去当那个坏人
and I will be the bad guy.
叫我校长
Call me Headmaster.
你会以我为豪的
I'll make you proud.
我要毁掉霍普·迈克尔森
I will destroy Hope Mikaelson.
怪物们回来了
The monsters are back.
我不知道这是怎么回事
I have no idea how or why
也不知道它自己会不会停止
or if it's gonna stop.
我施了黑魔法
I did black magic.
你说你有办法能帮忙
You said you had something that could help.
我觉得起作用了
I think it's working.
是的
Yes, it is.
我找到让所有人回想起被马里之洼
I found a way to bring back everyone's
夺取的记忆的办法了
Malivore memories.
你确实还记得她
You do remember her.
这下一切都变了  对吗
That changes things, right?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
*我不该说我爱过她
* I was wrong to say I loved her *
*不该认为我是对的
* I was wrong to think I'm right *
*当我告诉她一切都结束了
* When I told her it was over *
*我亲爱的人啊  我说了谎
* My darling, I had lied *
*我一直在逃离我心中的恶魔  担心
* I've been running from my demons, afraid to... *
你有没有那种记忆
Have you ever had a memory where you can't tell
你也说不清是真的发生过还是只是梦到过
if it actually happened or if it was just a dream?
*担心我找到的真相
* Afraid of what I'd find *
你也想不清楚这个问题  只好不再去想
Your head can't make sense of it, so you let it go.
只能说服自己这只是自己的幻想
You convince yourself it was your imagination.
*当我无法喜欢上现在的自己
* But how am I supposed to love you *
*又谈何会去爱你
* When I don't love who I am? *
*当我支离破碎
* And how can I give you all of me *
*又如何为你全情付出
* When I'm only half a man? *
*我现在就像一艘自毁的沉船
* 'Cause I'm a sinking ship that's burning *
*放开我吧
* So let go of my hand *
*我如何全情为你
* Oh, how can I give you all of me... *
万一你意识到这并不是梦呢
What if you realize it wasn't a dream at all?
那是真的
It was real.
全部都是真的
It was all real.
*没人可以
* No one can ever... *
我来守护传送门啦
Reporting for portal duty!
*伤害自己
* Hurt myself... *
我带了后援
I brought backup.
*我是一颗沉石
* 'Cause I'm made out of stone *
*无人可救
* And I'm beyond help... *
崭新的一天开始了
And so you start a new day,
你的心里要装负着原本不需要去想的事
armed with everything you never thought you needed to know...
*对于我来说
* To me... *
背负着无人去做的那个决定
...burdened with a choice no one should have to make...
*当我无法喜欢现在的自己
* But how am I supposed to love you *
*又谈何爱你
* When I don't love... *
所有的人都关注着你做出正确的决定
...knowing all eyes are on you to do the right thing.
那么  现在
So, this is...
很棒  是吧
nice, right?
聚在一起
Together again.
- 很好  - 了不起
- It's great. - It's awesome.
对于你们俩来说  就为了抢夺一个花园小矮人
I mean, for the two of you not to be talking to each other
不和对方说话
just because you're competing for the love
就不和对方说话了
of the same garden gnome...
女人还远不止谈情说爱吧
I think we're more evolved than that as women.
- 当然了  - 毫无疑问
- Absolutely. - Without a doubt.
很好  就我来说呢
Good. Because, personally,
我现在感觉非常好
I've never been better.
我的努力是值得的
My work paid off.
思维明锐
My mind is sharp.
那些被人察觉出的精神崩溃
All perceived mental breakdowns were
都是由两个控制欲极强的吸血鬼
a figment of my imagination
所搞出来的幻想
fed by two manipulative vampires
这两个吸血鬼会永远是我的敌人
who will remain forever my enemies.
塞巴斯提安怎么样了
What's going on with Sebastian?
唐顿庄园校长想要我们召他进来
Headmaster Downton Abbey wants us to enroll him
好让他不要到街上去
to keep him off the streets.
但是他之前让我觉得自己脑子出问题了
But after deliberately letting me think that I was unwell,
所以我肯定不会给他这个机会
I will not let that happen.
你应该原谅MG
You should forgive MG.
永远都不会
Never.
他不是故意想伤害你
He didn't want to hurt you.
他对我有所隐瞒
He hid things from me.
差评
Zero stars.
他不是唯一一个对朋友保守秘密的人
He's not the only friend keeping secrets.
我也不是想故意伤害你
I didn't want to hurt you either.
是啊  差评呗
Yeah, well, zero stars.
那就是传说中的棱镜吗
Is that what I think it is?
是的
Yeah.
给
Here.
我不需要这个了
I don't need it anymore.
谢了
Thanks.
瞧瞧我们
Look at us.
身心如此愉悦
Clear hearts and minds.
我们要理性过好这一天
Letting the power of our intellect rule the day
不要被感性操纵
over our emotions.
体面优雅地向前看
Moving forward with dignity and grace.
这就是女性力量的真正含义
This is the true definition of girl power.
我为我们骄傲
I'm proud of us.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
你们好啊  女巫们
Greetings, witches.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
以答案换答案
An answer for an answer.
有两个姐妹
There are two sisters.
一个生下了另一个
One gives birth to the other.
另一个  反过来
And the other, in turn,
又生下了第一个
gives birth to the first.
他们是谁
Who are they?
他们
They're...?
白天与夜晚
Night and day.
那对姐妹是白天与黑夜
The sisters are Night and Day.
作为你答对的奖励  我回答你的问题
Your reward for answering correctly is to know that you
站在你们面前的就是古老国度的主人
are in the presence of the master of the ancient lands.
神圣
The all-holy,
永恒的斯芬克斯
ever-divine sphinx.
一般人听完都会很惊讶
People are usually more impressed.
这学期过的太久了
It's been a long semester.
定
Prohibere.
消失
Invisique.
瞧见了吧  女性力量
See? Girl power.
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第7集
当然了  瓦德穆斯校长
Headmaster Vardemus, please.
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
我会等你
I'll hold.
嘿  好消息
Hey. So, good news.
我们又抓到只怪物  友情提示  是斯芬克斯
We caught another monster. It's a sphinx,
以防你说马里之洼收集架上已经有了一只了
in case you had that on your Malivore bracket.
那么这应该代表
Which must mean that the zombie's
僵尸那些应该已经被撞死了吧  对吗
probably roadkill by now, right?
除非马里之洼现在开始
Unless Malivore is actually starting to send
一次派来两个怪物了
two monsters at a time,
那么  好吧
in which-- 'Kay.
翻 译  肉萨
早上好
Uh, good morning to you, too.
你跟我说过了你的故事
You told me your story.
但是现在
But now,
翻 译  MonicaSmiles
我回忆起来了
with the memories,
你能回来我就很开心了
I'm just happy to have you back.
我希望大家都有这种感觉
I wish everyone else felt the same.
翻 译  煎饼
你需要给他们时间
You're just gonna have to give them time.
翻 译  Carousel
其实
Actually...
我也这么打算的
planning on doing just that.
我要回新奥尔良做研究
I'm headed home to New Orleans to do research
调查怎样和我姑姑
on how to close the portal
还有她的女巫们关上传送门
with my aunt and her circle of witches.
我懂了
I see.
那么这次你去新奥尔良
Now, this trip to New Orleans,
特效：小螺号
还会回来吗  还是
is it round-trip or...
就不回来了
one-way?
老实说  我不知道
To be honest with you, I don't know.
校 对   MonicaSmiles
抱歉  我现在
I'm sorry I don't have
特 效   麦 斯
没办法直接回答你
a straight answer for you.
显然我很在乎你
I obviously care about you,
我也在乎霍普
and I care about Hope, too.
我已经失去了所谓的女性力量
Look, I have hit girl power rock bottom.
我不喜欢自己追问你这种问题
I hate myself for having to ask you this,
但就直说了吧
but cut to the chase.
你要选择谁
Who are you gonna choose?
我不知道  因为我不是他
I still don't know, because I'm not him.
我只是你潜意识折射的全息图像
I'm a prismatic hologram from your subconscious.
我只知道你了解的事
I only know what you know.
你要找到
You have to find out
- 他知道的事  - 没错  可他躲在
- what he knows. - Yeah, but he's holed up
图书馆  做调查
in the library, doing research
- 逃避一切  - 那你知道去哪里找到他了
- and avoiding everything. - Then you know where to find him.
- 可我要说什么呢  - 听着
- What do I say, though? - Look.
看着我
Look at me.
你还是想要他的  对吗
You still want him, right?
当然了
Of course I do.
不过大家都想要他  这就是问题所在
Everybody wants him, though. That's the problem.
甚至马里之洼都想夺走他
Malivore even wants him.
不能把这个模拟的你交出去太可惜了
It's too bad I can't just give them you.
但如果你可以呢
But what if you could?
你不用和我一起在这里
You know, you don't have to sit with me.
你肯定还有其他更有意义的事可以做
I'm sure you have better things you could be doing.
你在这我就在这里
If you're here, I'm here.
很好  但我相信你已经在我身边
That's cool, but I'm pretty sure you haven't left my side
整整22个小时了
for 22 straight hours.
如果怪物从霍普她们眼皮底下溜出来
And if a monster were to slip past the girls,
谁可以在这里保护你呢
who would have been right here to protect you?
可你是我兄弟
Yeah, but you're my brother.
不是我的保镖
You're not my bodyguard.
兰  只要能保证你安全我干嘛都可以
I'm whatever I need to be to keep you safe, Lan.
这是我欠你的
I owe it to you.
因为霍普吗
Because of Hope?
拉夫  你什么都
Raf, you don't owe me
- 不欠我的  - 这次
- anything. - Just let me
你就让我欠着
owe you this.
嗨
Hi.
我们可以聊聊吗
Any chance we can talk?
当然了
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
你们尽管聊
I'll give you guys some space.
嘿
Hey.
我有一个大胆的主意
I have a crazy idea.
这个大胆的主意
As crazy ideas go,
确实听着很大胆
this one certainly takes the cake.
但也可能成功
But it could work,
对吗
right?
应该是可以的
I suppose it could.
但这需要动用一定的
However, it would require a certain level
黑魔法  我知道你爸
of black magic, and I know how your father
不希望你接触这类的魔法
feels about you practicing such sorcery.
现在性命攸关
It's life or death.
他会理解我的
He'll deal.
严格来说
Technically...
这有可能成功
it is possible.
太好了
Sweet.
这柄三叉戟能帮上忙
This trident will be of use.
你真确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you're ready for this?
讲真  唯一一个会舍身犯险的只有
Technically, the only person who has to do anything dangerous
霍普
is Hope.
你觉得她会怎么说
What do you think she'll say?
大概会骂我们失心疯了
Probably that we lost our minds
要我们别乱逞英雄吧
and should stay out of the hero business.
那你又会怎么
And what will you say to her
说服她呢
in return to convince her?
看来只有一个法子能搞清楚了
I guess there's only one way to find out.
新奥尔良市
霍普
Hope!
别走
Don't go.
我需要你
I need you.
我必须想个法子
Uh, I-I have to figure out a...
关闭传送门
a way to close the portal.
那我跟你一起去
Then I'll come with you.
我不能再失去你了
I just couldn't stand losing you again.
霍普·迈克尔森  我爱你
I love you, Hope Mikaelson.
兰登  我也爱你
Landon, I love you, too.
我当然爱你了
Of course I love you.
卧槽
hell.
你是跑来找霍普的吗
You had to find Hope?
这是怎么回事
What the hell is happening?
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
这压根不是所谓的女性力量
This is the opposite of girl power.
你压根就没有好好想明白
This is the opposite of clear thinking.
现在有两个兰登吗
There are two Landons?
我们把另一个兰登叫做
We are calling the other one...
高仿兰登
SimuLandon.
我用棱镜
I used the prism
投射出了我的潜意识
to manifest my subconscious,
乔茜把它变成了活物
and then Josie turned him into a golem.
展示一下
Show her.
瓦德穆斯校长也帮了我们
Headmaster Vardemus helped us.
用个叫做三叉戟的东西
We used this object called a trident to bind
施咒将高仿兰登的思想躯体和灵魂融合在了一起
the mind, body and spirit of SimuLandon with a spell.
什么咒语
What kind of spell?
你就别担心这些啦
Nothing that you need to worry about.
他给了我一个神奇的沙漏
He gave me this weird magical hourglass
帮我消除副作用
that prevents any side effects.
乔茜  要是你沉迷黑魔法  爸爸会杀了你的
Josie, Dad will melt you if you're dabbling in black magic.
我没有沉迷  我只是为了关上传送门
I'm not dabbling. I'm doing what needs
行必行之事而已
to be done to close the portal.
我们要拿他做诱饵
We're gonna use him as a decoy.
让斯芬克斯带他进传送门
We'll let the sphinx take him into the portal.
我不想进去
I don't want to go in the portal.
我想和霍普在一起
I want to stay here with Hope.
我觉得要和你的潜意识谈谈
Uh, I think we need to talk to your subconscious
要尊重他人私人空间
about personal space.
我也没想到他会这么直白
I didn't realize he'd be so vocal.
腿脚也快
And fast.
我们一把他造出来他拔腿就跑了
He ran away after we created him.
他是想去找你吧
I guess to find you.
不过有个小问题
JOSIE: There's one catch, though.
他的生命力与月运周期息息相关
I bound him to the lunar cycle.
等到明晚月亮当空高照时
So, when the moon reaches its apex tomorrow night...
高仿兰登便会灰飞烟灭
Simu-me will disintegrate.
啥啥  怎么没人告诉过我
What? Uh, no one told me that part!
- 这法子有这么能关闭传送门呢  - 这时候就该你上场了
How does that close the portal? That's where you come in.
咱得把高仿兰登的血全部换成霍普的
We need to pump SimuLandon full of Hope's blood,
他一进去  传送门感应到了混血种的血脉便会自动关闭
so when he goes in, the Tribrid blood will close the portal.
只有我的血并不足以关闭传送门
My blood's not enough to keep the portal closed.
我得变身吸血鬼
I have to activate my vampire side.
马里之洼会把他丢出来
Malivore is just gonna spit him out
再新造一个传送门的
and create a new portal.
前提是要在他灰飞烟灭之前把他丢出来
Not if he disintegrates before there's anything to spit out.
这样就不会有新传送门出现了
Portal closed, no new portal opens.
一石二鸟
Both problems solved.
生活回归正常
Life goes back to normal...
差不多吧
...ish.
你觉得把兰登的潜意识
LIZZIE: And you thought it was smart
化成人形这样很明智吗
to give Landon's subconscious a voice?
这是我们能想到的唯一方法
It's the only way anyone could think of to close the portal.
也许  你只是想
Or maybe you just wanted him
让他直抒胸臆而已
to spill the beans about who he wants.
我已经知道他内心深处是这么想的了
Pretty sure I got that question answered already.
霍普  爱老虎油
I love you, Hope.
求求你别再说了
Please stop saying that.
我情难自已  我想站在楼顶上大声喊
- I can't help it-- I want to shout it from the rooftops.
- 我爱霍普  - 沉睡咒
- I love Hope-- Ad somnum.
我打死都不会让你
Look, I'm not letting you get
接近兰登的  别蹦跶了
anywhere near Landon, so...
我来逗个闷子
let's make this easy on both of us, okay?
有种生物
There is a creature.
早晨用四只脚走路
At the dawn of life, it has four feet.
中午用两只脚走路
At the middle, two feet.
傍晚用三只脚走路
And in its twilight, three feet.
打一种生物
What is it?
婴儿用四肢爬行
A baby walks on four feet,
长大了用两只脚走路
and then it stands on two feet.
到了晚年
And then when it gets old,
要拄着拐杖走路
it walks with a cane.
答案是人
The answer's man.
这题太简单啦
That's an easy one.
经典的斯芬克斯之谜
Classic riddle of the sphinx.
看来我是名过其实了
My reputation precedes me.
这书上还写了我的什么事迹
What else has been written about me?
各种都有
Uh, all sorts of things.
希腊人写了很多你谜语的故事
The Greeks were all about your riddles.
但据埃及神话
But according to Egyptian mythology,
斯芬克斯是他们的保护神
sphinxes were protectors.
守卫在神谕的庙宇外面
Stood guard outside the temples of oracles.
那么多书
So many books.
却都是杜撰的
So few facts.
我才不是神谕的保护者
I am not a protector of oracles.
我就是神
I am the oracle.
既然你猜对了
And seeing as you've answered
我的谜语  你可以问我
my riddle correctly, you've earned yourself
任何问题
an answer to any question.
怪物基础课上学的第一个知识点就是
- First thing they teach us in Monster 101--
别听怪物乱扯
don't listen to the monsters.
斯芬克斯不能撒谎
Sphinxes can't lie.
来嘛
Come on.
就问一个问题
One question won't hurt.
我唯一想问的问题就是
Look, the only question I have is...
我该怎么保护兰登不受马里之洼的伤害
how do I keep Landon safe from Malivore?
你刚看到了什么
What did you just see?
只要兰登还在这
There's no keeping Landon safe
就无法护他周全
as long as he remains here.
要是你想救他出马里之洼
You must get him out of this place
你必须让他离开这里
if you wish to keep him from Malivore.
准备好了吗
Ready?
话说
So...
你不想解释一下  为什么
we're not gonna talk about how you
在我们干掉恶魔之后  你为什么离开了我
walked away from me after we took down the Croatoan?
我没什么好说的
I didn't have much to say.
要说一句欢迎回来吗
Welcome back?
高仿兰登倒是有很多要说的
He has plenty to say.
他只是我的潜意识
He is my subconscious.
嘴上没个把门的
He has no filter.
我自认为我是个内心复杂又成熟的人
I am a complex, evolved being last time I checked.
成熟的人会与其他人沟通
Evolved people talk to one other.
要是事态复杂化了  他们是不会转身就走的
They don't just stalk off when things get complicated.
那你干嘛要躲着我
So why don't you stop avoiding me?
我没有躲你
I'm not avoiding you.
我俩这不是呆在同一间屋子里嘛
We're literally in the same room.
你懂我意思的
Oh, you know what I mean.
能说说你是怎么想的吗
Tell me how you feel.
重点不在于我怎么想
It's not about what I feel.
重点在于要做正确的事
It's about doing the right thing.
做正确的事
There's a shelf life
也是有期限的
on doing the right thing.
要是等待过久  那也是错
If you wait too long, it's just wrong.
你就没有什么别的要对我说的了
So you don't have anything else you want to say to me?
我爱你
I love you.
很爱很爱你
So much.
有大麻烦
We got a problem.
我告诉你
Oh.... I'll tell you who's
到底是谁有大麻烦了  瓦德穆斯
- got a problem-- Vardemus.
要是他觉得他可以把年轻的嗜血吸血鬼
If he thinks that he's allowed to enroll Teen Dracula
招进我女儿们的学校
in the same school as my daughters...
里克
Ric!
瓦德穆斯就是问题的根源
The problem is Vardemus.
还记得你要马克警长给我的
Those from the crime scene at the bar
那些酒吧现场的法医样本吗
that you had Sheriff Mac forward to me?
我终于拿到结果了
I finally got the results back
这是我在费城的女巫朋友寄来的
from a witch friend of mine in Philly.
结果与瓦德穆斯匹配
They're a match with Vardemus.
你查了瓦德穆斯的基因
Oh, you ran Vardemus' DNA.
我说了我会盯住他的
I told you I'd keep an eye on him.
但更奇怪的是  你瞧
But it gets weirder. Look.
等等  这结果不可能啊
Wait... his results don't make any sense.
上面显示  他既是男性又是女性
It says he's both male and female.
基因涵盖了世界上所有的种族
And every ethnicity under the sun?
但只有10%来源于白人
But only ten percent white,
我们都知道这不可能
which we both know is not true.
他也有犬类和鹿的基因
He's also part canine, part deer.
等等  我见过这结果
Wait, I've seen this before.
马里之洼的化验结果
At the Malivore pit,
霍普消失的那晚  除了她和兰登
the night Hope disappeared, there was a third person there,
还有第三个人在场
besides her and Landon.
我一直不知道那人是谁  直到现在
I couldn't figure out who it was until...
你是说当晚瓦德穆斯也在那吗
You're saying Vardemus was at the pit?
是他
Him...
或者说是假扮成他的怪物
or the monster pretending to be him.
高仿兰登到处乱跑
So, SimuLandon is running around
跟大家宣扬他爱霍普
telling everyone that he loves Hope.
看来我还不够好
I guess I'm second-rate.
才不是这样  萨尔茨曼小姐
Far from second-rate, Ms. Saltzman.
你是个厉害的女巫
You are a powerful witch now.
你还能承受住  没到喷鼻血的程度
And a long way from gushing nosebleeds.
你的进步真让我刮目相看
I'm impressed with your growth.
我都感觉自己要炸开了
I feel like I'm gonna explode.
那个沙漏是失效了吗
Has that hourglass stop working?
没有没有
Not at all.
但它只能抑制黑魔法而非情绪的波动
But it holds black magic, not strong emotions.
这不止是情绪波动
This is more than strong emotions.
我感觉我的大脑在尖叫
It feels like my head is screaming at me.
你朋友骗了你
Well, your friend lied to you.
你双胞胎妹妹帮她瞒着你
Your twin helped her keep that secret.
你男朋友
Your boyfriend's heart
显然爱着其他人
clearly belongs to another.
但是不用担心
But fear not.
还有其他的办法
There are other ways to release
可以释放你意识中的魔鬼
the demons dancing in your mind.
我们今早用的三叉戟
The trident we used this morning.
我相信
I believe
这对于你来说不是问题
you're finally strong enough for this.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
这个咒语
This spell
可以将你的愤怒
will channel the rage,
悲伤  和所有情绪
the sadness, everything...
疏导到这个物体里
into that object.
它可以从你身体里转移出
It will transfer all the dark energy
所有黑暗的能量
right out of you.
跟我重复
Repeat after me.
咒语
Phesmatos
tribum nas ex viras.
咒语
Quo animo transibit.
Phesmatos tribum
咒语
nas ex viras.
Quo animo transibit.
咒语
Phesmatos tribum
nas ex viras. Quo animo transibit.
咒语
Phesmatos tribum nas ex viras.
Quo animo transibit...
你可以做到的
You can do this.
集中注意力
Keep your focus.
咒语
Phesmatos tribum nas ex viras.
Quo animo transibit...
集中注意力
Keep your focus
在这个三叉戟
on the trident.
马上就完事了
This will all be over soon.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我都不知道我会这么害怕针
I didn't know I was so afraid of needles.
看来我有多了一个害怕的东西
I guess I'll have to add that to the list.
*我跑向你
* And I'll run to you... *
狭小的空间
Small spaces,
带翅膀的小虫子
um, bugs with wings,
有合叶的门
doors on hinges...
抱歉
Sorry.
我是话太多了吗
Am I talking too mu-- I just get--
我紧张的时候就会很能说
I get chatty when I'm nervous.
我们就好好坐在这儿等吧
Why don't we just sit and wait?
安安静静的  好吗
Okay? In silence?
好的
Okay.
*如果你需要一场战斗
* And I'll fall for you *
*我也愿为你而败
* If you need a fight... *
那你为什么离开镇上
So, why you leaving town?
你也害怕安静吗
You afraid of the quiet, too?
我快死了
I'm dead soon.
多聊聊天有什么伤害呢
What's the harm in talking?
我不想留下来是因为
I don't want to stay because I...
我不想留在一个不受人欢迎的地方
I don't want to be where I'm not welcome.
但是你属于这里
But you belong here.
这是为吸血鬼  女巫和狼人们开的学校
It's a school for vampires, witches and werewolves.
而你有这三种血统
You're all three.
我知道  规则上是说得通
Yeah, I know. On paper it makes sense,
但现实中
but in reality, it...
太复杂了
it's complicated.
有什么复杂的
What's so complicated?
*我会奔向你
* And I'll run to you... *
你朋友不想让你进
Your friends don't want you to have to go
传送门  所以他们创造了我
into the portal, so they created me
去送死
to die.
- 别那么说  - 没关系
- Don't say that. - It's okay.
这是事实
It's true.
确实很可怕
It's scary as hell,
但是为了保护你的安全我会做任何事
but I'm gonna do whatever it takes to keep you safe.
*即使失去光明
* If I lose my sight... *
你确实想什么就说什么
You really do say whatever's on your mind.
肯定是潜意识棱镜的锅
It must be the subconscious prism thing.
*如果你需要一场战斗
* If you need a fight *
*我会呼唤你
* I'd still call to you... *
很抱歉兰登一直说不出口
I'm sorry Landon doesn't.
*即使失去光明
* If I lose my sight... *
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我不怕承认自己是一个胆小鬼  但他怕
I'm not afraid to admit that I'm a coward, but he is.
所以他无法说出希望你留下
That's why he can't say he wants you to stay.
所以他现在不在这里
That's why he's not here right now
和你分享他对你的感受
sharing how he feels about you.
*当洪水开始蔓延
* When the waters rise *
*我会跑向你
* And I'll run to you... *
莉齐带我走之前
Can we hold hands before Lizzie comes
我们可以拉着手吗
to take me away?
*即使我什么都看不见了
* I'll still call to you *
*也会一直呼唤你
* If I do go blind *
*即使你在战斗中失败
* And I'll be all for you *
*我也会全心全意为你付出
* If you lose the fight. *
嘿  兰登
Hey, Landon.
嗨
Hi.
你干什么呢  兄弟
What are you doing, bro?
这是保护我免受怪物伤害的万全之策
It's a failsafe to protect me against the monster.
如果我沉到河底了
The sphinx can't take me if I'm dead
斯芬克斯就没办法带走我  对吗
at the bottom of a lake, right?
这太疯狂了
This is insane.
你是说高仿兰登吗
Yeah, you mean the SimuLandon?
我指的是一切
I mean everything.
你看看你自己在干什么
Do you even see what you're about to do to yourself?
我知道你是涅槃凤凰  你还会再活过来
I know that you're a phoenix and that you'll come back,
但你就仗着这个各种找死吗
but does that make it okay?
然后就出现了这些怪物  和攻击
And then there's these monsters and-and the attacks,
还有各种计划和各种备用计划
and-and the plans and the backup plans,
但是想想斯芬克斯说的
but according to the sphinx,
这一时半会儿不会结束的
it's not even gonna end any time soon.
斯芬克斯可以通灵吗
The sphinx is a psychic?
他可以预见到这个事吗
Does that mean he'll see this coming?
如果是又有什么关系吗
Does it even matter if he does?
因为你们只会又想到另外一种疯狂的解决办法
'Cause you guys are just gonna cook up another crazy solution.
我甚至不知道我们是怎么落到这步境地的
I don't even know how we got here.
我们来这个学校
We came to this school
是因为与我们而言  这里是最安全的地方
because there was nothing out there that was safe for us.
但现在感觉是
But now it feels like
这里是世界上最不安全的地方
this is the least safe place on Earth.
那个会通灵的斯芬克斯还对你说什么了
What else did the psychic sphinx tell you?
乔茜  乔茜
Oh, Josie. Josie.
宝贝
Baby.
爸爸
Dad.
我好像做错事了
I think I did something bad.
记住  就很平常的走到他身边
Remember, just casually walk by him
只要斯芬克斯看到你
and as soon as the sphinx sees you,
我就会用魔法打开牢门
I'll use magic to open the bars
他会抓走你
and then he'll grab you
带着他的新玩具回到马里之洼
and take his new toy back to Malivore.
明明是很可怕恐怖的事
You make this sound easy and fun
听你说完觉得非常简单有趣
when it's actually gruesome and terrifying.
现在就去吧
Go. Now.
兰登·柯比
Landon Kirby.
芝麻开门
Patentibus.
我要拿你怎么办呢
And what exactly do I do with you?
我不需要你
I have no need for you.
不好意思
Excuse me?
是的  安全了  宝贝
Yes! Safe, baby.
你脑子里是一团毛线吗
Did a hairball get lodged in your brain?
他可是兰登·柯比
That's Landon Kirby.
世上独一无二的他
The one and only.
所有从传送门来的怪物
Every monster that comes out of that portal
都想抓他回马里之洼
wants him for Malivore.
我来这不是为了兰登·柯比
I am not here for Landon Kirby.
那你他妈来这干什么
Why the hell are you here, then?
一个答案换一个答案
An answer for an answer.
你还是省省你的字谜吧
Enough with the riddles.
好吧
Fine.
我可以回答你的问题
I'll answer your question...
很好
Great.
但是是以字谜的形式
...in the form of a riddle.
靠
Dammit.
黑暗之中  浮现一道光
In blackness, a light emerges,
为黑暗的灵魂照亮一道指引的路
illuminating the path for darkened souls to follow.
其中两个人各走各的路  但第三个人见到了一条新路
Two forge their own way, but a third sees a new path.
这条新路是什么
What is the new path?
放轻松
Take it easy.
学校已经把其他人疏散出去了
The school's been evacuated,
你现在绝对不能移动
and you're in no shape to move.
你在这里很安全
You'll be safe here.
怎么了
What's going on?
总之  瓦德穆斯校长
In a nutshell, Headmaster Vardemus
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
是克拉克探员的伪装
was a trojan horse for Agent Clarke,
斯芬克斯并不想要兰登
and the sphinx doesn't want Landon
原因还没有人可以破译
for reasons no one can decipher,
乔茜不小心创造出了一个黑暗物质
and Josie accidentally created
现在摸不清他的能力
a dark object of indeterminate power.
- 我要帮忙  - 不
- I should help. - No, hey.
你身体里的血液只够维持你的呼吸
You have just enough blood in your veins to breathe.
躺在这里好好疗伤
Lie here and heal
我去学校巡逻
while I go and patrol the school.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
嘿
Oh, hey.
想我了吗
Miss me?
克拉克  你怎么进来的
Clarke? How did you get in here?
我最可靠的戒指
My trusty ring.
创造了幻象
Creates illusions.
我想着你朋友都被疏散出学校了
I thought I'd camp out while your friends
我可以来这里扎营
emptied out the school.
- 冲击波  - 惊喜吧
- Fluctus Inpulsa. - Surprise.
我在学校军械库找到的
I found these in the school armory.
施了咒语的手铐可以使女巫的咒语失效
Spelled shackles that neutralize a witch's power.
里克又一项对抗超自然能力的保护
Yet another of Ric's failsafes against supernaturals.
是啊  随便坐  不用拘束
Yeah, please, go ahead, make yourself comfortable.
既然你来了  告诉我你来这干什么
And while you're at it, tell me what the hell you're doing here.
我对我父亲发誓
I swore to my father I would
我会回来带你走
come back and take you out,
但是
but my dad
我爸爸又一次耍了我
screwed me over yet again.
他又干嘛了
How did he do that? Hmm?
他看着像一位非常可爱又富有超自然能力的领导
He seems like such a lovely supernatural mastermind.
当时我的形态开始瓦解
My form started to break down.
他为了控制我给我限制了时间
He put a ticking clock on me in order to control me.
不得不靠吃人和怪物来稳定自己的情况
I had to consume people and monsters to stay stable.
可没什么用
Well, it didn't work.
我烧掉了那些用来吃的怪物
I burned through my monster food supply
可还是不稳定
and I was still unstable.
一旦是泥人  终究是泥人
Once a mud man, always a mud man.
但再也不是了
But not anymore.
我有一个新的办法
I have a new solution.
你
You.
当我有能力变成混血种彻底对抗我父亲时
Why kill you when I can become a powerful Tribrid
我又何必要杀了你
and stand up to my father once and for all?
所有人都想变成混血
Ah, everybody wants to be a Tribrid
但也要有法子真能变成混血才可以
until they actually have to be a Tribrid.
那是什么
What is that?
一件你好朋友乔茜
Mm, a little weapon
今天帮忙创造出的小武器
your frenemy Josie helped create today.
现在  我的意识
Now my consciousness
会转到我下一个伤害的人身上
will transfer into the next person I cut.
我知道我不该幸灾乐祸  可是
I know I shouldn't gloat, but...
谁叫你当初扔下我
you screwed me over.
是时候遭报应了
And now I get payback.
我要享受这个过程
I'm going to enjoy this.
你现在身上一滴血都没有
You literally have no blood.
你觉得你能跑多远
How far do you think you can get?
霍普
Hope?
Hope.
作为一个全能生物
For an all-powerful being,
你可不擅长躲猫猫啊
you're not great at hide and seek.
真聪明
Clever girl.
玩这些小把戏
Cute little trick.
快开门  霍普
Now open the door, Hope.
你个狗东
Son of a...
来人啊
Somebody help!
救命
你无处可逃  没人会来帮你的
Nowhere to go, no one to help you.
你好啊  哥哥
Hello, brother.
我听见你的喊叫声了  你受伤了吗
I heard you scream. Are you hurt?
你来了就好多了
Better now that you're here.
应该是你跳进马里之洼里
You should have jumped into the pit
而不是你的小女朋友
instead of your little girlfriend.
你俩又和好了吗
Are you guys back together?
感情那些子事  有时候真是难懂啊
The relationship drama-- it's so hard to keep up with sometimes.
- 我已经听倦了你的声音  - 别担心
- So tired of hearing your voice. - Don't worry.
你也不用听很久了
You won't have to hear it much longer.
我真是不懂了
I just don't get it.
懂啥
Oh. Get what?
- 我们老爸看上了你啥  - 是啊  你可以
- What our father sees in you. - Sure, you can
重生  可你没有魔法
regenerate, but you have no magic.
总有人得冲上去救你
Someone always has to swoop in and save you.
你真可悲  我不在乎
You're pathetic. I don't care
你或者老爸是怎么看我的
what you or our father think of me.
我只在乎她
I only care about her.
抱歉  霍普  这是我们的家事
Sorry, Hope. This is family business.
- 好吧  真了不起  - 别这么觉得
- Okay, I'm impressed. - Don't be.
他将永远低我一等  逊色于我
He'll always be the inferior son.
可这场面  我看倒未必
Well, it doesn't look like it from this angle.
动手啊
Just do it.
你不需要她
You don't need her.
你需要的是我
You need me.
- 动手啊  - 兰登  住手
- Do it. - Landon, no!
- 我这是为了你  霍普  - 别
- This is for you, Hope. - No!
这不是我计划之中的  可起码凤凰是永生的
Not what I planned, but at least phoenixes are immortal.
明天死的可是你了
Now you die tomorrow.
我赢了
Boom. I rule.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
风水轮流转啊
this just took a turn.
- 你要对我施咒了  对吧  - 是啊
- You're gonna whammy me, aren't you? - I am.
记住啊  我可是已经克服了那
Remember that I'm already dealing with the trauma
知道自己将死的心理创伤啊
of knowing I'm dying.
- 我会记住的  - 这牺牲
- I will. - Kind of makes the whole sacrifice
还有几分浪漫  不是吗
a little less romantic, though, no?
现在什么情况
I mean, where is the real deal?
他现在肯定不再喜欢他另一个女朋
He must be off with his other girlfr...
我今天学到了  无论我们多努力
I learned today that, no matter how hard we try,
我们都解决不了怪物的问题的
we can't solve the monster problem.
很抱歉这么做
I'm sorry to do this.
我真心想避免这份痛苦
I really wanted to avoid this pain,
可这已经过去够久了
but it's been long enough.
我能帮你拿些什么吗
Can I get you anything?
阿司匹林  冰块  或是苏打汽水
Aspirin? Ice? A sparkling soda?
不用了  不过你可以坐下陪陪我
No, but you can sit down.
抱歉兰登那臭小子的事我没站你这边
I'm sorry I didn't have your back with mud boy.
我真的很高兴你没事
And I'm really glad that you're okay.
嗨  我能和乔茜聊会儿吗
Uh, hi. Can I talk to Josie for a sec?
我去拿些冰块
I'll go and get some ice.
有时  痛苦无法避免
And sometimes pain is unavoidable.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
被利用了
Used.
但我很庆幸你没事
But I'm glad you're okay.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
嗯  还好  就是感觉有点力竭了
Yeah. Yeah, I'm just a little drained.
这样啊  我知道这种感觉
Yeah, I know the feeling.
嗯
Yeah.
你该休息休息
You should get some rest.
会的
Oh, yeah, I will.
但是
But, um...
我想知道  你同不同意
I wanted to know if it was okay with you
我回学校
if I came back to school.
我想念学校的生活了
I miss it.
我想念课堂
I miss my classes.
想念早会
Miss morning meetings.
超能小队
Super Squad.
我甚至还很想念对我刻薄的丽兹
I even miss Lizzie being mean to me.
我想你
I miss you.
但
But, um,
如果我回来会让你更痛苦的话
I won't come back if my being here...
我就不回了
brings you any more pain.
那是什么声音
What's that?
佩内洛普的火书
Penelope's burn book.
一定是有人在用她的笔
Somebody must be using her pen.
*如果你能
* If you would have just... *
我已经意识到
I've come to the realization
问题不单单在于怪物们
that monsters aren't the only problem.
我也是问题所在
I'm the problem, too.
我就是所有痛苦的源泉
I am at the center of all this heartache.
怎么了
What is it?
- *他们让我忘记  - 是兰登
- * They tell me to forget * - Um, it's Landon.
*但我不想忘
* And I don't want to... *
所以  我得离开神秘瀑布镇
So I have to leave Mystic Falls,
既然他们会跟着我
knowing that they'll follow me.
我得让你们的生活远离这些怪物
I have to let you live your lives without monsters
远离我
and without me.
我希望你们有朝一日能原谅我所做的这一切
I hope you can forgive me for this someday,
如果你们不原谅的话  我也能理解
but I understand if you don't.
附着爱与忏悔呈上  兰登
With love and regret, Landon.
你确定要跟我一起吗
You sure about coming with me?
绝对的  老哥
All in, brother.
*姑娘  反正你也好了
* "Girl, you are better off anyway" *
*因为我知道那不是真的
* 'Cause I know that's not true *
*我想要你
* I want you *
*想要你是那个
* Wanted you to be the one *
*留下的人
* Who stayed *
*我怎能忘了你
* How can I black out you? *
他做出他的决定了
He made his choice.
我们也能做出自己的选择
We can make our own.
*你
* You... *
不管有没有兰登  你都属于这儿
Landon or no Landon, you belong here.
我希望你能留下来
I want you to stay.
*插入我唇的钉和针
* Pin and needles in my lips *
*无法麻醉
* No anesthetic... *
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
*我怎么能把你忘了
* How can I black out you? *
似乎
Something told me
我得把冰块
I needed to upgrade from ice
升级为冰淇淋
to ice cream.
*你
* You *
*我怎能忘了你
* How can I black out you? *
我敢说我们大家现在内心都
I can tell we are all feeling a lot of emotions
很复杂
right now.
*你
* You... *
所以  拿着
So get this.
老爸说在他确保
Dad says that I'm not allowed
塞巴斯蒂安的状况之前  我不能赶他走
to give Sebastian the boot until he has checked him out.
而现在没有校长了
And now that there's no headmaster,
MG也不会因为自己
no one is going to punish
狡猾的小手段而受罚了
MG for his weaselly little ways.
真是搞笑
How ridiculous is that?
*一直都是你
* It's always been you. *
丽兹跟我说过斯芬克斯的谜题了
Lizzie told me the sphinx's riddle.
很难解
It's a tough one.
是啊  我想知道他说的黑暗的灵魂什么意思
Yeah. I wonder what he meant by "darkened souls."
他是指鬼魂吗
Did he mean spirits?
有可能  还有件事
It's possible. Hey, by the way,
我就是想说
uh, I just wanted to say,
我不该投反对你的票的
I should've never voted you out.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不该让你身处那种境地的
Well, I... I should have never put you in that position,
错不完全在你  我也有责任
so we can both share the blame.
说不定斯芬克斯不是在说
Hey, what if the sphinx isn't talking
鬼魂  如果是怪物们呢
about spirits, but about monsters?
每个从马里之洼中出来的怪物都怀着同样的目的
Every one of them that came out of Malivore had the same agenda.
- 他们行动是有模式的  - 是的
- They all follow the same path. - Right.
但我还是搞不清  到底是哪两个怪物各走各的路
But I still don't get which two forged their own way.
黑暗之中  浮现一道光
In blackness, a light emerges.
是指神秘瀑布镇的传送门
The portal in Mystic Falls.
为黑暗的灵魂照亮一道指引的路
Illuminating the path for darkened souls to follow.
就是说从传送门里跑出来的生物
The creatures that emerged from the portal.
有两个各走各的路
Two forge their own way.
是指霍普和克拉克
Hope and Clarke.
可第三个  见到了一条新路
But a third... sees a new path.
也就是你
You.
你不是从命于马里之洼的
You don't serve Malivore
因为你看到了一条新路
because you see a new path.
你从命于新主人
You serve a new master.
干得漂亮
Well done.
你们解出了我的谜题
You solved my riddle.
马里之洼糟透了
Malivore is terrible,
可你们即将面临的
but what's coming...
会更糟
...is even worse.
你知晓神谕  那
you're the oracle, so
就告诉我们
tell us.
接下来会发生什么
What's coming next?
有两个囚犯
There are two prisoners.
一个是他囚笼的主人
One is the master of his cage.
另一个回家  却能力全无
The other returns home without power.
父亲的罪孽被降至这儿的女儿们身上
The sins of the father are visited upon the daughters here.
可又不在这
And not here.
新英雄出现了
New hero rises
但却会被金色的箭击倒
but can be felled by the golden arrow.
藏于你们中的豺狼有许多模样
The wolf among you has many faces.
当时间不存在时
When time fractures,
黑暗也将袭来
darkness overwhelms.
但最恐怖的毁灭之物
But the greatest destroyer of all...
还是爱
is love.
别担心
Don't worry.
一切都将变得无比明晰
It will all be painfully clear soon enough.
既然如今那男孩已经摆脱了马里之洼的控制
Now that the boy is away from Malivore's grasp,
我的使命就完成了
my work here is done.
再会
Until we meet again.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）